<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Copyright © 2013 Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.  All Rights Reserved.
QTI Proprietary and Confidential.
-->
<feature
      id="com.qualcomm.feature.ide.hexagon.opendsp"
      label="Hexagon OpenDSP"
      version="2.0.0.202108261310"
      provider-name="QUALCOMM">

   <description url="http://www.qualcomm.com">
      This feature includes OpenDSP code templates and examples
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.qualcomm.com">
      Copyright © 2013 Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.  All Rights Reserved.
QTI Proprietary and Confidential.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.qualcomm.com">
      Qualcomm Technologies, Inc Software User Agreement
2013

BEFORE YOU CLICK ON THE ‘I AGREE’ BUTTON, CAREFULLY READ THE
TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW. BY CLICKING ON THE ‘I AGREE’
BUTTON, YOU ARE AGREEING TO AND CONSENTING TO BE BOUND BY THESE
TERMS AND CONDITIONS. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS
AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW, CLICK THE ‘I DISAGREE’ BUTTON
AND THE SOFTWARE WILL NOT BE ACCESSIBLE TO YOU.
Confidentiality.
The Software is provided to you in accordance with the terms
of applicable Agreement(s) (Hexagon Access Tools Software License, AMSS agreement,  DSP Access Addendum, Nondisclosure Agreement, etc.) between Qualcomm Technologies, Inc and your company (the “Agreement”).
The Software and supporting documentation or information to which
you have access contains information that is confidential and
proprietary to Qualcomm and is transmitted in accordance with
the confidentiality provisions of such Agreements. In accessing
the Software which contains Qualcomm confidential and proprietary
information, you agree to hold such information in confidence
and to disclose the information contained therein only to others
who have a need to know as permitted under the terms of your
Agreement with Qualcomm.
Use. The Information contained herein is provided solely for
internal use by you and your company in accordance with the use
provisions outlined in the Agreement. You represent and warrant
that your use of such Information shall be in accordance with
the terms of the Agreements.
Termination.
All Software and supporting documentation or information shall
remain the sole property of Qualcomm, and in the event of any
termination or expiration of your Agreement with Qualcomm, you
shall immediately (i) return to Qualcomm the Information, and
any copies or updates thereof or certify in writing that all
such materials have been destroyed, and (ii) cease using, or
permitting to be used, the Software in accordance with the termination
provisions set forth in the Agreement.
This software may be subject to U.S. and international export,
re-export, or transfer (“export”) laws. Diversion contrary to
U.S. and international law is strictly prohibited.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import feature="com.qualcomm.feature.ide" version="1.5.0.qualifier"/>
      <import feature="com.qualcomm.feature.ide.hexagon" version="1.5.0.qualifier"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import feature="com.qualcomm.feature.ide.hexagon.hlos.interface" version="1.1.0.qualifier"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.qualcomm.hexagon.project.templates"
         download-size="189"
         install-size="5090"
         version="2.0.0.202108261310"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
